questions = [dict() for x in range(201)]
questions[0] = {"question" : "The emblem on the flag of the Republic of Tajikistan features a sunrise over mountains below what symbol?","answer" : "Crown"}
questions[1] = {"question" : "In Fukuoka, Japan, there's a hotel that costs just 65p a night. Why is it so cheap?", "answer" : "You're live-streamed on YouTube"}
questions[2] = {"question" : "Before they discovered mercury, thermometers were filled with what?", "answer" : "Brandy"}
questions[3] = {"question" : "In 1970, how did Oregon Highway Division dispose of a dead sperm whale?", "answer" : "Blew it up with dynamite"}
questions[4] = {"question" : "To try and get free cornflakes, Kellogs ran an ad encouraging women to do what?", "answer" : "Wink at the shopkeeper"}
questions[5] = {"question" : "The MOBA in Massachusetts stands for \"Museum Of what\"?", "answer" : "Bad Art"}
questions[6] = {"question" : "Yellowstone National Park in the US has two-thirds of the world's what?", "answer" : "Geysers"}
questions[7] = {"question" : "Why was the artwork 'Take the Money and Run' by Jens Haaning controversial?", "answer" : "It was a blank canvas"}
questions[8] = {"question" : "A 91-year-old man discovered he had been posting his letters where, for the last two years?", "answer" : "A dog poo bin"}
questions[9] = {"question" : "The Chipko movement involves doing what to trees, in order to protect them?", "answer" : "Hugging them"}
questions[10] = {"question" : "In the 1980s what was a 'zeek'", "answer" : "An attractive nerd"}
questions[11] = {"question" : "Originally, what were cartoon superheroes the Powerpuff Girls going to be called?", "answer" : "Whoopass Girls"}
questions[12] = {"question" : "In Ashbourne, UK, an annual event challenges people to use only their toes to do what?", "answer" : "Wrestle"}
questions[13] = {"question" : "Shakespeare wrote a curse against whom on his tombstone?", "answer" : "Grave robbers"}
questions[14] = {"question" : "What did Mary Shelley keep as a memento to remember her dead husband?", "answer" : "His heart"}
questions[15] = {"question" : "How did mobster Joseph \"Junior Lollipops\" Carna get his nickname?", "answer" : "His dad owned a cafe called \"Lolly's\""}
questions[16] = {"question" : "Why did people avoid Brussels sprouts in Medieval Britain?", "answer" : "They thought they contained demons"}
questions[17] = {"question" : "In 1933, a 24-hour phone hotline was set up in the UK. What service did it offer?", "answer" : "Told you the time"}
questions[18] = {"question" : "In the 1970s, what did MI5 try using to detect if someone was lying?", "answer" : "Gerbils"}
questions[19] = {"question" : "Professors in Sweden made a bet to place as many what in their research articles as possible", "answer" : "Bob Dylan lyrics"}
questions[20] = {"question" : "During the Industrial Revolution in Britain, what did a 'knocker-upper' do?", "answer" : "Wake people up"}
questions[21] = {"question" : "In bingo, what name is given to the number 46?", "answer" : "Up to tricks"}
questions[22] = {"question" : "What did a man in India cover his phone with in order to avoid radiation?", "answer" : "Cow poo"}
questions[23] = {"question" : "What did students in Volusia County, Florida, unexpectedly find in a vending machine?", "answer" : "A raccoon"}
questions[24] = {"question" : "What did Albert Einstein say was the most difficult thing to understand? Income taxes"}
questions[25] = {"question" : "The first-ever tennis balls were stuffed with what?", "answer" : "Human hair"}
questions[26] = {"question" : "The emperor Claudius legalized doing what at banquets?", "answer" : "Farting"}
questions[27] = {"question" : "Which horror film was originally called Whimpy?", "answer" : "Psycho"}
questions[28] = {"question" : "In Old English, what was a 'Wink-a-Puss'?", "answer" : "Owl"}
questions[29] = {"question" : "In 1968, 'The Sword of Damocles' was the name given to the first ever what?", "answer" : "Virtual reality headset"}
questions[30] = {"question" : "The official club for scientists with long hair is called what?", "answer" : " The Luxuriant Flowing Hair Club"}
questions[31] = {"question" : "What is Cookie Monster's first name?", "answer" : "Sid"}
questions[32] = {"question" : "In New Dehli, India, you can call an ambulance if what non-human thing falls sick?", "answer" : "A Tree"}
questions[33] = {"question" : "In Wales in the 1840s, how did farmers protest against the introduction of tollbooths?", "answer" : "They rioted while dressed as women"}
questions[34] = {"question" : "In New Zealand in the 1930s, what happened when farmers used a new weed killer?", "answer" : "It set fire to their trousers"}
questions[35] = {"question" : "In the Victorian era people with 'Pteridomania' were addicted to collecting what?", "answer" : "Ferns"}
questions[36] = {"question" : "The society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Long-Haired Men was set up by who?", "answer" : "David Bowie"}
questions[37] = {"question" : "What is the old-English nurse rhyme Three Blind Mice actually about?", "answer" : "Executing traitors"}
questions[38] = {"question" : "What did English leader Oliver Cromwell ban in 1644?", "answer" : "Christmas Day"}
questions[39] = {"question" : "What did a fire chief blame after two fires in one day in a UK town?", "answer" : "Exploding tea towels"}
questions[40] = {"question" : "What special title is given to the head of the UK Roundabout Appreciation Society?", "answer" : "The Lord of the Rings"}
questions[41] = {"question" : "Saturday Morning is the name of a beer flavored with what?", "answer" : "Lucky Charms"}
questions[42] = {"question" : "At 'Night of the Radishes' in Mexico, what do people do with radishes?", "answer" : "Carve them into art"}
questions[43] = {"question" : "To prove themselves, boys in an Amazonian tribe must do what?", "answer" : "Wear ant-filled gloves"}
questions[44] = {"question" : "What are 'Waterloo Teeth'?", "answer" : "False teeth made from dead people's teeth"}
questions[45] = {"question" : "Alchemist John Dee was said to be a spy for Queen Elizabeth I. How did he sign his letters to her?", "answer" : "007"}
questions[46] = {"question" : "In Ancient Greece, why did the philosopher Empedocles jump into a volcano?", "answer" : "To show he was a god"}
questions[47] = {"question" : "In 1769, eccentric trader Timothy Dexter exported what to the Caribbean?", "answer" : "Stray cats"}
questions[48] = {"question" : "In 2019 in the UK, what got inside of an arcade claw machine?", "answer" : "A toddler"}
questions[49] = {"question" : "A woman from Bristol, UK, got stuck in a bathroom window trying to do what?", "answer" : "Throw her poo out the window"}
questions[50] = {"question" : "In 1900, what did the curator of the Smithsonian predict people would have in the future?", "answer" : "Flying refrigerators"}
questions[51] = {"question" : "A sculpture in Vancouver called 'Device to Route Out Evil' is shaped like a what? Upside-down church"}
questions[52] = {"question" : "Gwyneth Paltrow's company 'goop' sells what to help protect your aura?", "answer" : "Psychic vampire repellent"}
questions[53] = {"question" : "In Dominica, a 'Mountain Chicken' is actually a what?", "answer" : "Giant frog"}
questions[54] = {"question" : "In Ch√¢teauneuf-du-Pape, France, it is illegal to do what in vineyards?", "answer" : "Land a flying saucer"}
questions[55] = {"question" : "What did french artist Aquabouse use to paint cows?", "answer" : "Cow poo"}
questions[56] = {"question" : "What are 15% of women estimated to do on Valentines's Day?", "answer" : "Send themselves flowers"}
questions[57] = {"question" : "In Cornwall, UK, it is illegal to trespass unless you are climbing a tree to do what?", "answer" : "Point at fish"}
questions[58] = {"question" : "In Australia, it is illegal to dress up as who?", "answer" : "Batman"}
questions[59] = {"question" : "In Old English, what was a 'Bobby-Dazzler'?", "answer" : "A butterfly"}
questions[60] = {"question" : "In 2019, what happened to a poacher after he shot a rhino in a South African National Park?", "answer" : "He was trampled by an elephant"}
questions[61] = {"question" : "Mr Goxx is a hamster who helps people make decisions about what?", "answer" : "Buying and selling crypto-currency"}
questions[62] = {"question" : "Just outside Susami, Japan, the world's first underwater what was installed?", "answer" : "Mailbox"}
questions[63] = {"question" : "Walt Disney said that he loved Mickey Mouse more than what?", "answer" : "Any woman he had met"}
questions[64] = {"question" : "A Boston orchestra, whose music is all about 'office work', uses only what to make their music?", "answer" : "Typewriters"}
questions[65] = {"question" : "Founded in 1922, what quality unites the members of the Caterpillar Club?", "answer" : "All parachuted from crashing planes"}
questions[66] = {"question" : "In Palau in the Western Pacific, what is the national dish?", "answer" : "Bat soup"}
questions[67] = {"question" : "The average American does what 22 times a day?", "answer" : "Opens the fridge"}
questions[68] = {"question" : "What does Kylie Minogue have a phobia of?", "answer" : "Clothes hangers"}
questions[69] = {"question" : "What might a medieval doctor prescribe for asthma?", "answer" : "Boiled frog"}
questions[70] = {"question" : "Alfred Hitchcock was terrified of what?", "answer" : "Eggs"}
questions[71] = {"question" : "At Lake Superior University in the US, what tradition has gone on since 1971?", "answer" : "Unicorn hunting"}
questions[72] = {"question" : "In 1567, in Braunau, Austria, the mayor died in a very strange way. How?", "answer" : "Tripped over his beard"}
questions[73] = {"question" : "What was US president Ronald Reagan's first ever job?", "answer" : "Lifeguard"}
questions[74] = {"question" : "The 'Pluto Lamp', invented in 1898, was a cross between a street lamp and a what?", "answer" : "Hot drinks machine"}
questions[75] = {"question" : "A woman's car broke down in Pittsburgh, USA. What was the engine full of?", "answer" : " Walnuts"}
questions[76] = {"question" : "In 1899 in New York, Jacob German was given the world's first what?", "answer" : "Speeding ticket"}
questions[77] = {"question" : "Other than boxing, what unusual hobby does Mike Tyson enjoy?"}
questions[78] = {"question" : "In 1999, hackers discovered that any Hotmail account could be accessed using what password?", "answer" : "Eh"}
questions[79] = {"question" : "In 2007, Kevin Shelley broke 46 what, with his head in a minute? Toilet seats"}
questions[80] = {"question" : "In Croatia, there's a museum of taxidermied frogs doing human activities. What is it called?", "answer" : "Froggyland"}
questions[81] = {"question" : "Thrash metal band Austrian Death Machine write songs based entirely on what?", "answer" : "Arnold Schwarzenegger movies"}
questions[82] = {"question" : "Some people believe that Sir Isaac Newton invented what for animals?", "answer" : "The cat flap"}
questions[83] = {"question" : "The ashes of American chemist Fredric Baur were buried inside which unusual item?", "answer" : "A pringles can"}
questions[84] = {"question" : "In the US state of Texas, what severely damaged a border protection radio tower?", "answer" : "Vulture vomit"}
questions[85] = {"question" : "Attila the Hun died on his honeymoon due to what?", "answer" : "Alcohol poisoning"}
questions[86] = {"question" : "What is an \"aglet\"?", "answer" : "The plastic tip of a shoelace"}
questions[87] = {"question" : "A Russian saying is: \"I'm not hanging what on your ears\"?", "answer" : "Noodles"}
questions[88] = {"question" : "What is the collective noun for a group of unicorns?", "answer" : "A blessing"}
questions[89] = {"question" : "What piece of Beatles memorabilia did dentist Michael Zuk buy for ¬£19,500?", "answer" : "John Lennon's tooth"}
questions[90] = {"question" : "The British Journal of Psychology published a study connecting exam scores with people's what?", "answer" : "Finger length"}
questions[91] = {"question" : "Researchers in the US believe that beards on men may have evolved to protect them from what?", "answer" : "Punches"}
questions[92] = {"question" : "What is responsible for most of the power outages in the United States?", "answer" : "Squirrels"}
questions[93] = {"question" : "In 2019, a woman from San Diego ate what in her sleep?", "answer" : "Her wedding ring"}
questions[94] = {"question" : "Abraham Lincoln excelled at what past-time?", "answer" : "Wrestling"}
questions[95] = {"question" : "What is it considered uncouth to do to a baguette in France?", "answer" : "Cut it with a knife"}
questions[96] = {"question" : "In Madagascar, what are pregnant women not allowed to do?", "answer" : "Wear a hat"}
questions[97] = {"question" : "What does someone suffering from 'Formication' think is happening to them?", "answer" : "Insects are crawling on them"}
questions[98] = {"question" : "What did some Victorians believe was a side-effect of riding on a train?", "answer" : "Madness"}
questions[99] = {"question" : "In 1845, who kept swearing loudly at the funeral of US president Andrew Jackson?", "answer" : "His parrot"}
questions[100] = {"question" : "At the Nakizumo festival in Japan, what is it traditional for sumo wrestlers to do?", "answer" : "Make babies cry"}
questions[101] = {"question" : "In France, what is it illegal to call your pig?", "answer" : "Napoleon"}
questions[102] = {"question" : "In the US city of Boston, it is illegal to have what in the back seat of your car?", "answer" : "Gorillas"}
questions[103] = {"question" : "What unexpected hobby does Ryan Gosling enjoy?", "answer" : "Knitting"}
questions[104] = {"question" : "What did the ancient Greeks use for toilet paper?", "answer" : "Stones"}
questions[105] = {"question" : "Who did the U.S Government issue with a pilots licence in 1927?", "answer" : "Santa Claus"}
questions[106] = {"question" : "In 2021, there was a spike in people selling what innocent item on the  black market?", "answer" : "Lego"}
questions[107] = {"question" : "In 2009, an accountant in New Zealand got fired for doing what?", "answer" : "Writing emails in all caps"}
questions[108] = {"question" : "What was Bubble Wrap originally marketed as?", "answer" : "Wallpaper"}
questions[109] = {"question" : "In 2008, what item shaped like the state of Illinois, did two sisters sell on eBay for $1350?", "answer" : "A cornflake"}
questions[110] = {"question" : "In 2018, what did a 70-year-old couple do to their neighbour to get a restraining order?", "answer" : "Sprayed them with a hose"}
questions[111] = {"question" : "According to the 'Aetherius Society', who is alive and living on Venus?", "answer" : "Jesus"}
questions[112] = {"question" : "Before Madonna was famous, she was fired from Dunkin' Donuts for doing what?", "answer" : "Squirting jam"}
questions[113] = {"question" : "In Armenia they have a saying: \"Stop ironing my what\"?", "answer" : "Head"}
questions[114] = {"question" : "Before it was considered a condiment, ketchup was sold as a what?", "answer" : "Cure for diarrhoea"}
questions[115] = {"question" : "The Greeks and Romans used which unusual material as a bandage?", "answer" : "Spiderwebs"}
questions[116] = {"question" : "In 2019, a man managed to open a small safe locked for 49 years. What was inside?", "answer" : "A waitress' notebook"}
questions[117] = {"question" : "What did inventory Huge Gernsback do to avoid any distractions?", "answer" : "He wore a wooden helmet"}
questions[118] = {"question" : "What is the name of the monster who is said to live near Murphysboro, Illinois?", "answer" : "Big Muddy Monster"}
questions[119] = {"question" : "An old Arabic saying is: \"God gives what to a man with no teeth\"?", "answer" : "Nuts"}
questions[120] = {"question" : "In Switzerland, what is it illegal to do after 10pm?", "answer" : "Flush the toilet"}
questions[121] = {"question" : "President Jimmy Carter was attacked in his fishing boat by what?", "answer" : "A swamp rabbit"}
questions[122] = {"question" : "Research by the University of Colorado found that cat owners were more likely to be what?", "answer" : "Entrepreneurs"}
questions[123] = {"question" : "In Dummerstorf, Germany, they have invented a toilet for cattle. What is it called?", "answer" : "MooLoo"}
questions[124] = {"question" : "25% of Americans believe that which fictional character was real?", "answer" : "Sherlock Holmes"}
questions[125] = {"question" : "What unusual hobby does Taylor Swift enjoy?", "answer" : "Making snow globes"}
questions[126] = {"question" : "In Irvine, California, what was found in a Costco hot dog?", "answer" : "A bullet"}
questions[127] = {"question" : "In 1989, the Soviet Union traded three battleships and 17 submarines for what?", "answer" : "Bottles of Pepsi"}
questions[128] = {"question" : "In 1988 an unusual sport was invented at Ohio State University. What was it?", "answer" : "Squirrel fishing"}
questions[129] = {"question" : "In 2021, people jumped out of their cars on a California highway to collect what from a tipped truck?", "answer" : "Cash"}
questions[130] = {"question" : "Indian man Shridhar Chillal holds the world record for having the longest what?", "answer" : "Fingernails"}
questions[131] = {"question" : "In the US state of Texas, it is illegal to do what to a neighbour's cow?", "answer" : "Milk it"}
questions[132] = {"question" : "In North Dakota, what are you not allowed to do while wearing a hat?", "answer" : "Dance"}
questions[133] = {"question" : "What does the old English word \"Bouffage\" mean?", "answer" : "Nice dinner"}
questions[134] = {"question" : "In Thailand, what is it illegal to leave home without?", "answer" : "Underpants"}
questions[135] = {"question" : "Alectryomancy uses what to predict the future?", "answer" : "Chickens"}
questions[136] = {"question" : "When Koko the Gorilla was asked, \"Where do gorillas go when they die?\" she signed back what?", "answer" : "A comfortable hole"}
questions[137] = {"question" : "In LA, there is a street performer called 'The Venice Beach Glass Man'. What is his act?", "answer" : "He walks on broken glass"}
questions[138] = {"question" : "The world's biggest potato was given a name. What was it?", "answer" : "Doug"}
questions[139] = {"question" : "During his crossing of America in 1803, Meriwether Lewis' dog died. How?", "answer" : "He ate it"}
questions[140] = {"question" : "In the US state of Texas, it is illegal to swear in from of what?", "answer" : "A corpse"}
questions[141] = {"question" : "In Greece, what do children do with their baby teeth?", "answer" : "Throw them on the roof"}
questions[142] = {"question" : "What does the old English word \"Twattle\" mean?", "answer" : "Gossip"}
questions[143] = {"question" : "In Switzerland it is illegal to own just one what?", "answer" : "Guinea pig"}
questions[144] = {"question" : "If you suffer from a condition called boanthropy, you believe that you are what?", "answer" : "A cow"}
questions[145] = {"question" : "What happened when two Buddhists released captive lobsters into the wild for good karma?", "answer" : "They were fined"}
questions[146] = {"question" : "A British astronomer played an April Fools' prank on UK citizens by tricking them to do what?", "answer" : "Jump at  the same time"}
questions[147] = {"question" : "A New York woman in her 60s started a business where you can rent what for $40 an hour?", "answer" : "A mum"}
questions[148] = {"question" : "After 16 years, a Swedish woman found her lost wedding ring attached to what?", "answer" : "A carrot"}
questions[149] = {"question" : "In 2019, what mistake did a burglar in Toronto make before leaving the crime scene?", "answer" : "He photocopied his face"}
questions[150] = {"question" : "In 1996, what did an American woman use to remove a corn from her foot?", "answer" : "A shotgun"}
questions[151] = {"question" : "What did the Russian defence minister do with the remains of some 3000-year old warriors?", "answer" : "He tried to clone them"}
questions[152] = {"question" : "In medieval England, what was sometimes used instead of money?", "answer" : "Eels"}
questions[153] = {"question" : "In the Phillippines, what surprising dish do they serve in McDonald's?", "answer" : "Spaghetti"}
questions[154] = {"question" : "In Kentucky in 1876, what strange thing rained down from the sky?", "answer" : "Meat"}
questions[155] = {"question" : "What name was originally given to the Spice Girls?", "answer" : "Touch"}
questions[156] = {"question" : "In Christchurch, New Zealand, the city council used to pay someone to be their official what?", "answer" : "Wizard"}
questions[157] = {"question" : "In WWII, what did the Royal Navy call a cat who survived being on three ships that sank?", "answer" : "Unsinkable Sam"}
questions[158] = {"question" : "What was the first-ever ice hockey puck made from?", "answer" : "Frozen cow poo"}
questions[159] = {"question" : "What is it illegal to throw in Alabama?", "answer" : "Confetti"}
questions[160] = {"question" : "After the events of The Wizard of Oz, what does Tin Man have an argument with?", "answer" : "His own detached head"}
questions[161] = {"question" : "In Arizona, what is it illegal to put in your bathtub after 7pm?", "answer" : "A donkey"}
questions[162] = {"question" : "Queen Elizabeth II was a fully trained what?", "answer" : "Mechanic"}
questions[163] = {"question" : "An acquired taste, Casu Martzu is a cheese containing what unusual ingredient?", "answer" : "Maggots"}
questions[164] = {"question" : "What did Roman Emperor Caecus ban for nearly 200 years?", "answer" : "The letter Z"}
questions[165] = {"question" : "If someone is playing with a 'quockerwodger ', what are they playing with?", "answer" : "A puppet"}
questions[166] = {"question" : "In 1984, what caused the space shuttle Discovery to malfunction?", "answer" : "An icicle of pee"}
questions[167] = {"question" : "In the USA, Washinton police officers get a half-hour class in how to what?", "answer" : "Sit down"}
questions[168] = {"question" : "What does Adele have a fear of?", "answer" : "Seagulls"}
questions[169] = {"question" : "What did the Mongols eat to cure a hangover?", "answer" : "Pickled sheep's eyes"}
questions[170] = {"question" : "What fulfilled the role of mayor of Talkeetna, Alaska, for 20 years?", "answer" : "A cat"}
questions[171] = {"question" : "In 1777, Frederick the Great asked his subjects to do what in the mornings?", "answer" : "Drink beer"}
questions[172] = {"question" : "Inventor Nikola Tesla never married, but claimed to have fallen in love with what instead?", "answer" : "A pigeon"}
questions[173] = {"question" : "What kind of museum would you find in Avanos, Turkey?", "answer" : "A hair museum"}
questions[174] = {"question" : "What was the name of Walk Disney's first ever character?", "answer" : "Oswald the Lucky Rabbit"}
questions[175] = {"question" : "In Greek myth, Lycurgus mistook his son for a what?", "answer" : "A plant"}
questions[176] = {"question" : "In Brazil, a man was killed when what fell through his roof?", "answer" : "A cow"}
questions[177] = {"question" : "What surprising item is found inside every British tank?", "answer" : "A kettle to make tea"}
questions[178] = {"question" : "In 1518 a mysterious plague struck Strasbourg. What did it do to people?", "answer" : "Make them dance"}
questions[179] = {"question" : "In the 1950s, 'Popular Mechanica' magazine predicted what would be eliminated by the year 2000?", "answer" : "Hurricanes"}
questions[180] = {"question" : "What did champion 'gurner' Peter Jackman do to secure his fifth championship win?", "answer" : "Had his teeth removed"}
questions[181] = {"question" : "During WWII, the Polish army found a tame bear. What did they do with it?", "answer" : "Made it an officer"}
questions[182] = {"question" : "Every year 40,000 Americans are injured in the home by what?", "answer" : "Toilets"}
questions[183] = {"question" : "What did the ancient Egyptians do when their cat died?", "answer" : "Shaved off their own eyebrows"}
questions[184] = {"question" : "What does the old English word \"Wagpastie\" mean?", "answer" : "Bad person"}
questions[185] = {"question" : "In Western Australia, it is illegal to own over 50kg of which normally legal item?", "answer" : "Potatoes"}
questions[186] = {"question" : "What did Adeline and Augusta van Buren get repeatedly arrested for in 1916 while crossing America?", "answer" : "Wearing trousers"}
questions[187] = {"question" : "What did composer Edvard Grieg carry around in his pocket for good luck?", "answer" : "A frog figurine"}
questions[188] = {"question" : "If something has a \"natiform\" shape, what does it resemble?", "answer" : "Buttocks"}
questions[189] = {"question" : "A man from Australia tried to sue his boss for $900,000 for doing what?", "answer" : "Farting next to him"}
questions[190] = {"question" : "What item worth $407,000 was stolen from a Spanish hotel in 2021?", "answer" : "A bottle of wine"}
questions[191] = {"question" : "Coprastastaphobia is the fear of what?", "answer" : "Constipation"}
questions[192] = {"question" : "In El Colacho, Spain, the tradition is for a man dressed as the devil to jump over what?", "answer" : "Babies"}
questions[193] = {"question" : "What is the collective noun for a group of jellyfish", "answer" : "A smack"}
questions[194] = {"question" : "On the 4th Jan in the USA it's National what day?", "answer" : "Spaghetti Day"}
questions[195] = {"question" : "In the movie Braveheart, what was accidentally filmed in the background during a battle scene?", "answer" : "A car"}
questions[196] = {"question" : "What was the movie Back to the Future originally going to be called?", "answer" : "Spaceman from Pluto"}
questions[197] = {"question" : "A 66-year-old lost weight by eating what every day?", "answer" : "A Christmas dinner"}
questions[198] = {"question" : "What is baseball player Dusty Baker credited with inventing in 1977?", "answer" : "The high five"}
questions[199] = {"question" : "After being in zero gravity, what did astronaut Scott Kelly discover had changed about himself?", "answer" : "He was taller"}
questions[200] = {"question" : "On Sunday in Florida it is illegal for a single woman to do what?", "answer" : "Skydive"}